<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Camera Tips</string>
    <string name="first_str">One of the reasons raw is such a superior format for digital photography is that a raw image stands the test of time. So long as it doesn’t get corrupted or deleted, you can save out JPEG or TIFF images from the original raw file for eternity. \nIt’s just like a film negative, in other words. Every time you edit and save out from a JPEG file, however, there is a bit more image degradation. Shooting JPEG all the time is a process of diminishing returns.</string>
    <string name="second_str">How do you focus? Chances are you half press the shutter button, maybe waiting until you see the green focus-confirmation dot or hear the beep, then take the shot. Then you keep changing between single AF and continuous (AI Servo) depending on the subject. \nBy using back button focusing, via the AF On button, you can stay in continuous AF mode all the time to track subjects. You can still achieve focus lock as you do with AF S mode, however, for static subjects. \nIn other words you can save time and fiddling. Check out back-button focusing today – there is a reason many action and wedding photographers swear by it.</string>
    <string name="third_str">While auto-everything exposure and ‘everything on’ AF can be dangerous and limiting, auto ISO actually has its uses for the serious photographer. If the light keeps changing, your camera can calculate and activate a more suitable ISO in a fraction of the time that you can. \nIf you are worried about noise creeping in, restrict the upper limit of auto ISO to 1600, but don’t be too conservative. Better a slightly noisy image than a soft one.</string>
    <string name="forth_str">It’s actually the central AF point which is the most sensitive, so try to use this whenever you can, using AF ‘lock and recompose’ where necessary. \nThat said, a relatively new camera with powerful autofocus features will have sensitive AF points across the viewfinder, so if you are in a hurry, quickly the select AF point that is closest to the part of the subject that must be in focus.</string>
    <string name="fifth_str">If you need to shift to manual focus, make life as easy for yourself as possible. Switch to Live View and you can zoom into the scene so you can check that critical areas are in sharp focus. If you have a compact system camera you may have ‘focus peaking’ too, which reveals which areas of the shot are in focus. Check your manual.</string>
    <string name="txt_title_str">Your Camera</string>
    <string name="btn_1_text">Tip 1</string>
    <string name="btn_2_text">Tip 2</string>
    <string name="btn_3_text">Tip 3</string>
    <string name="btn_4_text">Tip 4</string>
    <string name="btn_5_text">Tip 5</string>
    <string name="btn2_text">Tip 2</string>
</resources>
